Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
  - Area L - Western, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    - Cornwall, Falmouth and Cambourne, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/491; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/492; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, St. Ives, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/493; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, Truro, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/494; 1.0 file
    - Exeter, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/495; 1.0 file
    - Plymouth, Devonport, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/496; 1.0 file
    - Plymouth, Sutton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/497; 1.0 file
    - Torquay, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/498; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Honiton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/499; 1.0 file
    - Devon, North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/500; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Tavistock, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/501; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Tiverton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/502; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Torrington, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/503; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Torrington, By-Electon, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/503; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Totnes, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/504; 1.0 file
    - Bath, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/505; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Bridgwater, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/506; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/507; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Taunton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/508; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Wells, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/509; 1.0 file
    - [Somerset, Weston-super-Mare], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/510/1
    - Somerset, Weston-super-Mare By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/510/2; 1.0 file
    - [Somerset, Yeovil], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/511
  - Area M - Wales and Monmouthshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/512-CCO 1/12/547
    - Anglesey, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/512; 1.0 file
    - Brecon and Radnor, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/513; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Caernarvon, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/514; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Conway, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/515; 1.0 file
    - Cardigan, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/516; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/517/1; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/517/2; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Llanelly, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/518; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/519; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/520; 1.0 file
    - Flint East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/521; 1.0 file
    - Flint West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/522; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/523; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/524; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff South East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/525; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/526; 1.0 file
    - Merthyr Tydfil, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/527/1; 1.0 file
    - South East Wales Group, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/527/2; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/528; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/529; 1.0 file
    - Swansea East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/530; 1.0 file
    - Swansea West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/531/1; 1.0 file
    - South Wales Group, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/531/2; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Aberavon, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/532; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Barry, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/533; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Caerphilly, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/534; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Gower, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/535; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Neath, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/536; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Ogmore, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/537; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Pontypridd, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/538/1; 1.0 file
    - South West Wales Group, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/538/2; 1.0 file
    - Merioneth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/539; 1.0 file
    - Newport, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/540; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/541; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Bedwellty, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/542; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Ebbw Vale, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/543; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Monmouth, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/544; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/545/1; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, By-Election (file A), Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/545/2; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/545/3; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/546; 1.0 file
    - Pembroke, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/547; 1.0 file
  - Area N - Scotland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/548-CCO 1/12/618
    - Aberdeen North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/548; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeen South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/549; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/550/1; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire East, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/550/2; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/551; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire, Dundee, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/552/553; 1.0 file
    - [Angus and Kincardineshire, Dundee East], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; [CCO 1/12/552]
    - [Angus and Kincardineshire, Dundee West], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; [CCO 1/12/553]
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, North Angus and Mearns, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/554; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kircardineshire, Angus South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/555; 1.0 file
    - Argyll, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/556/1; 1.0 file
    - Argyll, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/556/2; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Ayr, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/557; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Bute and North Ayrshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/558; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Central Ayrshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/559; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Kilmarnock, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/560; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, South Ayrshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/561; 1.0 file
    - Banffshire, Banff, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/562; 1.0 file
    - Berwick and East Lothian, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/563; 1.0 file
    - Caithness and Sutherland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/564; 1.0 file
    - Dumfries, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/565; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/566; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/567; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Dunfermline Burghs, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/568; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Kirkaldy Burghs, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/569; 1.0 file
    - Fife, East Fife, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/570; 1.0 file
    - Fife, West Fife, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/571; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Inverness, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/572; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Ross and Cromarty, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/573; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Western Isles, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/574; 1.0 file
    - Kircudbrightshire and Wigtownshire, Galloway, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/575; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Bridgeton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/576; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Cathcart, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/577; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Central, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/578; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Craigton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/579; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Gorbels, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/580; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Govan, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/581; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Hillhead, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/582; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Kelvingrove, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/583/1; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Kelvingrove, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/583/2; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Maryhill, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/584; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Pollock, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/585; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Provan, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/586; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Scotstoun, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/587; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Shettleston, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/588; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Springburn, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/589; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Woodside, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/590; 1.0 file
    - Coatbridge and Airdrie, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/591; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Bothwell, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/592; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Hamilton, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/593; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Lanark, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/594; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Motherwell, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/595; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, North, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/596; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Rutherglen, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/597; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Central, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/598; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/599; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh, Leith, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/600; 1.0 file
    - [Edinburgh North], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/601
    - Edinburgh, Pentlands, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/602; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/603/1; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, By-Election, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/603/2; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh West, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/604; 1.0 file
    - Midlothian, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/605; 1.0 file
    - Roxburgh, Selkirk and Peebles, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/606; 1.0 file
    - Moray and Nairnshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/607; 1.0 file
    - Orkney and Zetland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/608; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Kinross and West Perthshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/609; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Perth and East Perthshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/610; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/611; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, Paisley, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/612; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, East Renfrewshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/613; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, West Renfrewshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/614; 1.0 file
    - Stirling and Falkirk Burghs, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/615; 1.0 file
    - [Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, Clackmannan and East Stirlingshire], Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/616
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, West Stirlingshire, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/617; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/618; 1.0 file
  - Area O - Northern Ireland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959
    CCO 1/12/619-CCO 1/12/630
    - Northern Ireland, Mar 1957-Feb 1959; CCO 1/12/619/630; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Mar 1959-Nov 1961
  This entire series of files is missing, with the single exception of CCO 1/13/201
  - Penistone, By-Election, Mar 1959-Nov 1961; CCO 1/13/201; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
  - Area A - Greater London, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    CCO 1/14/1-CCO 1/14/104
    - [Vacant], [Dec 1961-Jan 1968] Dec 1961-Jan 1968; [CCO 1/14/1-11]
    - Bromley, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/12; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/13; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/14; 1.0 file
    - Carshalton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/15; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/16; 1.0 file
    - Chislehurst, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/17; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/18/1; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/18/2; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/18/3; 1.0 file
    - Croydon North East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/19; 1.0 file
    - Croydon North West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/20; 1.0 file
    - Croydon South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/21; 1.0 file
    - Dagenham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/22; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/23/1; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/23/2; 1.0 file
    - Ealing North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/24; 1.0 file
    - Ealing South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/25; 1.0 file
    - East Ham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/26/27; 1.0 file
    - East Ham North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/26; 1.0 file
    - East Ham South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/27; 1.0 file
    - East Surrey, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/28; 1.0 file
    - Edmonton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/29; 1.0 file
    - Enfield, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/30/31; 1.0 file
    - Enfield East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/30; 1.0 file
    - Enfield West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/31; 1.0 file
    - Epping, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/32; 1.0 file
    - Erith and Crayford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/33/1; 1.0 file
    - Erith and Crayford, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/33/2; 1.0 file
    - Feltham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/34; 1.0 file
    - Finchley, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/35; 1.0 file
    - Fulham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/36; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/37; 1.0 file
    - Hackney Central, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/38; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/39; 1.0 file
    - [Hampstead], [Dec 1961-Jan 1968] Dec 1961-Jan 1968; [CCO 1/14/40]
    - Harrow Central, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/41; 1.0 file
    - Harrow East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/42; 1.0 file
    - Harrow West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/43; 1.0 file
    - Hayes and Harlington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/44; 1.0 file
    - Hendon North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/45; 1.0 file
    - Hendon South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/46; 1.0 file
    - Heston and Isleworth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/47; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/48; 1.0 file
    - Hornchurch, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/49; 1.0 file
    - Hornsey, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/50; 1.0 file
    - Ilford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/51/52; 1.0 file
    - Ilford North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/51; 1.0 file
    - Ilford South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/52; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/53; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/54; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/55; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/56; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/57; 1.0 file
    - Kingston upon Thames, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/58; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Brixton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/59; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Norwood, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/60; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Vauxhall, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/61; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/62; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/63; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/64; 1.0 file
    - Leyton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/65/1; 1.0 file
    - Leyton, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/65/2; 1.0 file
    - Merton and Morden, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/66; 1.0 file
    - Mitcham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/67; 1.0 file
    - Orpington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/68/1; 1.0 file
    - Orpington, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/68/2; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/69; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/70; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/71; 1.0 file
    - Richmond, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/72; 1.0 file
    - Romford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/73; 1.0 file
    - Ruislip Northwood, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/74; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/75; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/76; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/77; 1.0 file
    - Southall, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/78; 1.0 file
    - Southgate, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/79; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/80; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/81; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/82; 1.0 file
    - Surbiton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/83; 1.0 file
    - Sutton and Cheam, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/84; 1.0 file
    - Tottenham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/85; 1.0 file
    - Twickenham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/86; 1.0 file
    - Uxbridge, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/87; 1.0 file
    - Walthamstow, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/88/89; 1.0 file
    - Walthamstow East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/88; 1.0 file
    - Walthamstow West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/89/1; 1.0 file
    - Walthamstow West, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/89/2; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/90; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Clapham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/91; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Putney, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/92; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Streatham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/93; 1.0 file
    - Wanstead and Woodford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/94; 1.0 file
    - Wembley North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/95; 1.0 file
    - Wembley South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/96; 1.0 file
    - Westham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/97/98; 1.0 file
    - Westham North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/97; 1.0 file
    - Westham South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/98; 1.0 file
    - Willsden, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/99/100; 1.0 file
    - Willsden East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/99; 1.0 file
    - Willsden West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/100; 1.0 file
    - Wimbledon, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/101; 1.0 file
    - Wood Green, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/102; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/103; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/104/1; 1.0 file
    - Central Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/104/2; 1.0 file
    - North East London Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/104/3; 1.0 file
    - University of London Graduates, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/104/4; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    CCO 1/14/105-CCO 1/14/138
    - [Carlisle], [Dec 1961-Jan 1968] Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/105
    - [Cumbria, Penrith and the Border], [Dec 1961-Jan 1968] Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/106
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/107; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/108; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/109; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/110/111; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/110; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/111; 1.0 file
    - Jarrow, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/112; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/113; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/114/1; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, By-Election (file A), Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/114/2; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Deputy Chairman's file, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/114/3; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/115/116; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/115; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/116; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/117; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Aukland, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/118; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/119; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/120; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/121; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/122; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/123; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/124; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/125; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/126/1; 1.0 file
    - Durham West Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/126/2; 1.0 file
    - Durham Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/126/3; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/127; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/128; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/129; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/130; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/131; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/132; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/133; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/134; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/135; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/136; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/137/138; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/137/1; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/137/2; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/138/1; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, West, By-Election (file A), Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/138/2; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, West, By-Election - Deputy Chairman's file, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/138/3; 1.0 file
  - Area C - North West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    CCO 1/14/139-CCO 1/14/217
    - Altrincham and Sale, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/139/1; 1.0 file
    - Altrincham and Sale, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/139/2; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/140; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/141; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/142/143; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/142; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/143; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/144; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/145; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/146; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/147; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/148; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/149; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Nantwich, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/150; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/151; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/152; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/153; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/154; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/155; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-Under-Lyne, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/156; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in-Furness, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/157; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/158; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/159/160; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/159/1; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/159/2; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/160; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/161/162; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/161; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/162; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/163; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/164; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/165; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/166; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/167; 1.0 file
    - Leigh, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/168; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/169/177; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Edgehill, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/169; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Exchange, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/170; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Garston, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/171; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Kirkdale, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/172; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Scotland, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/173/1; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Scotland, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/173/2; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Toxteth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/174; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Walton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/175; 1.0 file